caribbeancinemas.com 2012-05-28

# Caribbean Cinemas of Puerto Rico -

Your privacy is important to us. We provide this statement to explain our practices and to inform you of your options regarding the way your information is collected and used at this site.

**COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION**

At Caribbean Cinemas site you will be able to join our movie club, subscribe to our newsletter and express an opinion. The types of personally identifiable information that we may collect in this site include: name, gender, address, e-mail address, birth date, occupation, telephone number, fax and information about your interest in and use of our services. You may also submit information about other people's e-mail address to let them know about this site. We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our site such as the type of browser and operating system you are using and the domain name of your internet service provider. We use the information you provide to fulfill your requests for our products and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other services that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also use this information to communicate with you, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter or to let you know about any changes to our terms of use. We use the information that you provide about others to offer our services to them. The movie reviews you submit are used to provide an interactive experience to users. When you submit this content for publication, we may publish your user name and other information you have provided us. We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to analyze and improve site usage and to enable us to personalize your experience. We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to a legal process such as a court order or subpoena, or to a law enforcement agency's request. The employees, agents and contractors of Caribbean Cinemas who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Statement. Although we take appropriate measures to protect your information we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner that is never used in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Statement.

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD PARTIES AND SPONSORS**

We will share the collected information only with our web host, who will use it to provide you with information about the services offered through as upcoming events and special offers. Our site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. Visitors should consult the other sites privacy notices since we have no control over information submitted to, or collected by these third parties.

**COOKIES**

Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. They are sometimes used to enhance your experience with internet sites. Cookies, by themselves do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering as a club member in our site. However, once you furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to be able to recognize you by name when you return to our site, save your password in any password-protected area and to enable you to use a shopping cart (when available). We may also use cookies to offer you programs or services.

**ABOUT SECURITY**

This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under age 13. No part of our website is designed to attract anyone under age 13.

**CHOICE/OPT-OUT**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from [Caribbeancinemas.com](http://www.caribbeancinemas.com/). You have the following options for removing your information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

    1.    You can send an email to info@caribbeancinemas.com  
    2.    You can send mail to the following postal address:  

                         **Caribbean Cinemas  
                         PO Box 19116  
                         San Juan, PR 00909**

**CONTACTING WEB SITE**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Caribbean Cinemas at 787-727-7137.
